mastiask.com 2010-08-23

# Privacy Policy

We are glad to welcome you to   MastiAsk. Please read this privacy statement to ensure that we are   committed to keeping secure the privacy of our members’ (customers)   details. This privacy policy outlines important information regarding the use and disclosure of User   information collected via the Website. MastiAsk  provides this privacy   policy to help Users make an informed decision as to whether to use or   continue using the website.

 **Collected Information** The information that we collect from the members using the site falls   into the following general categories:  
 **  
1\. User provided data**

Users may provide personally identifiable information (such as a name   and an email address) to MastiAsk when choosing to participate in the   various services available on the   website, such as sharing views via comment or feedback or other content   (collectively, the “Content”) for public viewing interests, entering   contests, accessing promotions, responding to surveys or other   personalized services (collectively, the “Services”).

 **2\. Cookies**

When you visit MastiAsk.com , we may   send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of   alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your   browser. MastiAsk.com may use both session cookies and persistent   cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser.   Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to   the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web   browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and   disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser   to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.   However, some features of the website may not function properly. Some of   our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.   These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to deliver   the advertisements and links that   appear on MastiAsk.com. They automatically receive your IP address   when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or   Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure   the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the   advertising content that you see.

MastiAsk.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective   privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed   information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to   opt-out of certain practices. MastiAsk.com’s privacy policy does not   apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other   advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may   do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information   about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the   browsers’ respective websites.

 **3\. Clear / transparent GIFs information:**

MastiAsk.com may choose to utilize   “clear .GIFs” to track the online usage patterns of our users in a   non-personally identifiable manner. Additionally, MastiAsk.com may also   use clear .GIFs in HTML-based emails dispatched to users so as to track   which emails are being opened by the recipients. This act helps   MastiAsk.com to determine active and inactive email addresses.

 **4\. Log data file information:**

When users log-in to their MastiAsk.com   account, our servers may automatically record and archive certain   information that web-browsers send whenever visiting a website. These   server logs may include information vital to validating the user’s   authorization to access the account. Information, such as a web request,   internet protocol (the “IP”) address, browser type, browser language,   referring pages, exit pages and visited URLs, platform type, click   counts, pages viewed and in what order, time spent, the date and time of   the request, and other important data is necessary to validate and   authorize a User’s entry and activity on the website.  
  **Use of information**

  * Personally identifiable information submitted by a user on   MastiAsk.com is used to operate, maintain, and provide features,   general and unique, of the website for the user’s use and pleasure.
  * All personal information, data, or content that you, the user,   voluntarily disclose to the website public areas become available to   other users and can be collected and used by others. Your email id, name   is displayed to other users when you comment on some story . Any   content that you submit (the “User Submission”) may be redistributed   throughout the Internet and other media channels, and/or may be viewed   by the general public through other means not controlled by   MastiAsk.com
  * MastiAsk.com does use your personally identifiable and certain   non-personally identifiable information, such as but not limited to,   anonymous user usage data, browser type, cookies, IP addresses, click   stream data, and the like, to improve the quality and use designs of the   Website through analysis of this data and trends.
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a)   remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during   your visit or the next time you visit the MastiAsk.com; (b) provide   custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the   effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics   such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your   entries, submissions, and status in promotions, and contests.
  * The site may include links to other websites and provides access to   products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies   we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third   party products or services through the site, use of any information you   provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site   you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

External Links, Content and Third-Party Advertising  MastiAsk.com is not responsible for the   content of external sites, nor are external sites to which links are   provided herein necessarily endorsed by MastiAsk.com. 

Recommended Links   and links to merchant affiliates are provided as additional resources   for our visitors, and at the time of review seemed to be suitable. We   cannot assure that all the links found on MastiAsk.com are safe to use,   if you are experiencing any difficulties with such links please contact   us at [webmaster@mastiask.com](http://www.techieask.com/privacy-policy/webmaster@celebrityask.com).  
We use third-party advertising companies   to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use   information (not including your name, address, email address, or   telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order   to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   If you would like more information about this practice and to know your   choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

One of our third-party advertiser   include Google.Google uses DART technology, use of the DART cookie   enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and   other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART   cookie by visiting the [Google   ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
